# TILDA DAHLGREN

+46 721 83 80 73 tilda.dahlgren@live.se www.tildadahlgren.com



## **SUMMARY**

Meticulous and structured person who works well in group as independently. I am a driven and stubborn person who always is motivated and comitted of achieving a good result.

After several years of working as a model has given me a tremendous tolerance, the oppertunity to travel all around the world by myself, and an ease to adapt to new environments and changes.

#### **EDUCATION**

Digital Data Strategist,
Hyper Island Stockholm
Information- and media technology,
Stockholms Tekniska Gymnasium
fall 2016 – spring 2018
fall 2011 – spring 2014

## **RELATED SKILLS**

Possesses a CaE (Certificate in Advanced English)
Possesses a Google Analytics Certificate
Programming skills in; HTML, CSS, Javascript
Comfortable using mutilple Adobe products as; Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Stockholmsgruppen Models  Model, Full time (Stockholm Sweden)	2008 –
Hollywood Model Management  Model, Full time (Los Angeles USA)	2015 – 2016
WE International AB Shop assistant, Part time	2015
ACNE Studios Warehouse, Part time	2014 – 2015
Wizard Models Model, Full time (Tokyo Japan)	2013 – 2014
UNO Models Model, Full time (Madrid Spain)	2013 – 2014
IMG Models  Model, Full time (New York USA, Paris France, Sydney Australia)	2010 – 2014